{
  "name": "Basic Math Quiz",
  "description": "This is a math quiz with basic arethmatic.",
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "What is 5 + 6?",
      "correctanswer": "11",
      "badanswers": ["12", "13", "10"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2 * 3?",
      "correctanswer": "6",
      "badanswers": ["2", "4", "5"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9 - 4?",
      "correctanswer": "5",
      "badanswers": ["3", "6", "4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 / 4?",
      "correctanswer": "2",
      "badanswers": ["1", "3", "4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 + 7?",
      "correctanswer": "10",
      "badanswers": ["9", "11", "12"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4 * 5?",
      "correctanswer": "20",
      "badanswers": ["21", "19", "18"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 - 1?",
      "correctanswer": "5",
      "badanswers": ["4", "7", "6"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 7 / 1?",
      "correctanswer": "7",
      "badanswers": ["6", "8", "5"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 + 10?",
      "correctanswer": "20",
      "badanswers": ["19", "21", "18"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5 * 2?",
      "correctanswer": "10",
      "badanswers": ["9", "11", "8"]
    }
  ]
}